{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the region was incorporated into Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the region was incorporated into Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved in 2025.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 10 November 1991, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the Nagorno-Karabakh Autonomous Oblast was established.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 10 November 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the Republic of Artsakh was established.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 26 December 1991, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became the Republic of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On December 10, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was dissolved in 2025.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was dissolved in 2023.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved in 2023.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was dissolved in 2023.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
      "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
      "frequency": 4
    }
  ]
}